Oh, you know, Monica's gonna freak if every box isn't labeled.
如果箱子上沒有標籤, 莫妮卡會生氣的
You're right, yeah. Okay..
好………
"Box of crap."
一箱……垃圾
It's so wild. When Monica and Chandler come back, they are gonna have a baby.
莫妮卡和錢德回來時會帶個孩子
-A baby! -I know.
-一個孩子！ -我知道
Wait. Ross doesn't know the baby's coming.
哦, 羅斯還不知道
Should we call and tell him?
打個電話？
I don't know. Rachel's still there yelling at him.
我不知道 瑞秋還在這衝他喊
Poor guy. I would not wanna be him right now.
可憐的傢伙.我現在可真不想成為他啊
Wait. Wait. Should we be doing this?
等一下, 我們該這樣嗎？
I don't know.
不知道
-It's probably not a really good idea. -Yeah, probably not.
-說不定是個好主意 -也許不是
-Well, that never stopped us before. -No, sir!
-我從來沒停過 -是啊
The Last One
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
I can't believe we're gonna be parents soon.
不敢相信幾小時後我們就成父母了
I can't believe it's three weeks early.
不能相信已經三個星期了
I love that our baby is prompt.
我愛我們的孩子, 他們就快出來了
Okay. All right, what room did the nurse say Erica was in?
剛才說艾瑞卡在哪兒？
-702. -Okay.
-702. -哦
-Come on, baby. -Come on. You can do this.
-來吧, 寶貝 -來吧, 你能行
Get this damn thing out of me!
快把那個鬼東西從我裡面弄出來！
Well, these are for you.
這是給你們的
Did you see the size of the thing that was coming out of that woman?
你看見那女人出東西的地方有多大嗎？
I couldn't tell who was giving birth to who.
我都不知道誰在生誰
-Hi. -Hey. How's it going?
-嗨 -嗨, 怎麼樣了？
It's okay. The doctor says it'll still be a while.
很好, 醫生說還要一會兒
-How do you feel? -Well, it hurts sometimes.
-感覺怎樣？ -有時候疼
Not too bad yet, though. It's a little scary.
不過不厲害 我有點害怕
Oh, I know. But, honey, you're gonna be fine.
我知道, 沒事的
Tell that to the lady in 702 with the toddler coming out of her.
告訴她那個702房生孩子的女人
I think that kid was wearing a shirt.
我想那個孩子是穿著衣服的
You're gonna be fine, though.
你沒事的
Hey.
嗨~
Go back to sleep. I have to go home.
接著睡吧, 我該回家了
Oh, God. This was amazing.
真是太棒了
It really was.
的確是太棒了
You've learned some new moves.
你學了不少新招兒嘛
Yeah, well, this guy at work gave me Sex for Dummies as a joke.
同事給我本《笨人性指南》想取笑我來著
-Who's laughing now? -I am.
-現在看誰笑到最後了 -沒錯呵
Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
呼氣、呼氣、呼氣
Okay. Good.
這樣就對了
Next time, can I say "breathe"?
下次我說呼氣行嗎？
No. Last time, you said it like Dracula, and it scared her.
不行, 剛才你說得像吸血鬼一樣, 嚇死她了
Do you want some more ice chips?
還要點東西嗎？冰片？
-No, I'm okay. -All right. I'll be right back.
-沒事, 不用了 -我馬上就回來
-Where you going? -To use the bathroom.
-去哪裡？ -洗手間啊
-You can't leave me alone with her. -What?
-別把我們倆丟在一起啊 -說什麼？
This is exactly the kind of social situation..
這是個很重要的場合
that I am not comfortable with.
我最怕的就是這種場合了
What kind of social situation are you comfortable with?
什麼樣的場合你不怕啊！
It's just that we've never spent any time, you know, alone together.
我和她從來沒單獨待在一起過
You'll be fine. You won't, but I'll be back in two minutes.
沒事的……才怪 不過我馬上就回來了
Okay.
哦
So any plans for the summer?
那個……夏天有什麼打算？
I don't know. Maybe church camp.
不清楚, 可能參加個教會野營吧
May not want to mention this.
哈……我為啥非要提這個
So you ever wonder which is worse?
有沒想過哪種情況更糟？
You know, going through labor or getting kicked in the nuts?
產前陣痛和老二被踢？
-What? -Oh, it's just interesting.
-說什麼？ -就是想想挺有意思的
Because no one will ever know because no one can experience both.
誰也不會知道的, 因為沒人兩種情況都能經歷吧
One of life's great unanswerable questions.
沒有答案的問題
Who knows? Maybe there's something even more painful than those things.
誰知道, 也許還有比那兩種情況更糟糕的呢！
Like this.
比如現在
-Come in. -Morning.
-進來 -早啊
-Hey. -What's that?
-嗨！ -什麼呀？！
Oh, it's my housewarming present for Monica and Chandler.
送莫妮卡和錢德的喬遷禮
That's a baby chick and duck.
剛出生的小雞和小鴨！
And I named them Chick Jr. and Duck Jr.
我給它倆取名叫小小雞和小小鴨
I did not see that coming.
真的是沒想到哈
They'll love it at that new house. It has that big backyard.
那麼大個後院它倆肯定會喜歡的
When they're old, they'll go to that farm..
以後要是老了的話 錢德可以和上次一樣把它們送到..
that Chandler took the other chick and duck to.
上次那個農場去
-Yes. -Yeah.
-沒錯 -是啊
-It's a shame people can't visit there. -That is the rule though.
-不過不能去看望實在是太不爽了 -沒辦法, 規矩就是這樣
-Guess what. You're almost an uncle. -What?
-好消息！你馬上就當舅舅了！ -嗯？
Erica went into labor. Monica and Chandler are at the hospital right now.
艾瑞卡昨晚要生了 莫妮卡和錢德現在正在醫院呢
-Oh, my God! -I have a feeling it's gonna be a girl.
-天哪！ -我敢肯定是個女孩
Phoebe, you were sure Ben was gonna be a girl.
你原來還猜本是個女孩來著呢
Have you seen him throw a ball?
從沒看過他扔球吧？
-Is Rachel here? -I think she's still asleep.
-瑞秋在不在？ -還在睡覺吧
How did it go with you guys last night? She seemed pretty pissed at you.
嗨！昨晚你倆怎麼樣了, 她好像怒了
We worked things out.
啊……後來事情解決了
What's that smile? Did something happen with you two?
笑啥呢？你倆是不是有點什麼事？
Hey, I'm not one to kiss and tell.
我這人辦完事以後不喜歡到處宣傳
But I'm also not one to have sex and shut up. We totally did it.
不過我也不會藏著不說  我倆做愛了
Oh, my God. You and Rachel?
天, 你和瑞秋？
-I know, it's pretty great. -So, what does that mean?
-是啊, 感覺太棒了 -意味著什麼啊？
-Are you guys getting back together? -Oh, I don't know.
-你們復合了？ -說不好
-We didn't really get to talk. -But do you want to get back together?
-我倆還沒仔細談過 -你自己想復合嗎？
I don't know.
不清楚啊……
It was incredible. I mean, it just felt so right.
真的是難以置信, 再合適不過了
When I was holding her, I mean, I never wanted to let her go.
我把她抱在懷裡時, 永遠都不想讓她離開
Know what? Yeah, I do. I want to be together.
嗯……沒錯, 我想和她在一起
So is she still going to Paris?
那她還去巴黎嗎？
Wow, I hadn't thought of that. I hope not.
還沒想過, 希望不會吧
This is, like, the best day ever. Ever. You guys might get back together.
今天太偉大了、太偉大了！ 你倆要復合
Monica and Chandler get their baby. There are chicks and ducks..
莫妮卡和錢德要有小孩 而且
in the world again.
世界上又有小雞小鴨了！
I feel like I'm in a musical.
啊~！感覺就像在音樂劇中一樣！
-Morning. -Guess you'll never know how it ends.
-早啊！ -永遠也唱不完整了……
-Hey. -Hi.
-嘿 -嗨！
-Hi. How'd you sleep? -Good. You?
-睡得怎樣？ -很好很好, 你呢？
-Good. -I'll bet you did.
-不錯 -那還用說
Would you guys mind giving us a minute?
啊……能讓我倆單獨待會兒嗎？
Sure. Just keep an eye on the chick and duck.
好, 幫忙看著點小雞和小鴨
Chick and the duck? Didn't they die..?
小雞和小鴨？不是已經死……
Dive. Yeah, they dove. Headfirst into fun on the farm.
死活非要去農場哦
So..
所以..
-Morning. -You too.
-早啊 -你也是啊
-Last night was just wonderful. -Oh, it really was.
-昨晚太棒了 -真的是
I woke up today with the biggest smile.
-我今天醒來滿臉都是笑容
I know, me too. It was..
-我也是啊
You know, it was one of those things you think is never going to happen.
就像……有些事情覺得從來不可能
And then it does, and it's everything you want it to be.
但有一天真的發生了 而且是自己所希望的那樣
I know. It was just..
我知道, 實在是……
It's just the perfect way to say goodbye.
實在是最好的告別方式了
-Just a little bit more, honey. -Oh, man, this hurts!
-再努力一點！ -疼死我了！
Is it really that bad?
真疼得那麼厲害？
I think it's time to kick you in the nuts and see which is worse.
啊哈！現在該踢你老二了, 看看哪個更疼！
The baby's head is crowning.
嬰兒的頭已經要出來了
Oh, my God! That is the most beautiful top of a head I have ever seen.
天哪！我所見過的最美麗的頭頂了！
-Chandler, you have to see this. -I'm okay.
-錢德！過來看！ -我就不用了
You don't want to miss this. This is the birth of your child.
錢德！絕不能錯過的！ 你孩子出生了！
-It's the miracle of life. -All right.
-生命的奇跡啊！ -好吧
Wow, that is one disgusting miracle.
哇！這麼噁心的奇跡！
Start pushing. Here we go.
開始往外擠
Here come the shoulders.
好！肩膀出來了！
It's a boy.
是個男孩！
-Is he okay? -He's just fine.
-他不要緊吧？！ -不要緊的
You did it.
你成功了！
It's a baby.
嬰兒！
A beautiful little baby. And some other stuff I'm gonna pretend I don't see.
美麗的小嬰兒！ 還有點其他東西我就裝沒看見吧！
-Would you like to cut the umbilical cord? -Okay.
-準備好切臍帶了嗎？ -好了
Well, that's spongy.
居然還一跳一跳的！
Hey, handsome.
嘿！我的寶貝兒,
I'll love you so much that no woman is ever gonna be good enough for you.
我愛死你了！誰家的女孩兒都配不上你！
-We are so lucky. -I know.
-咱們太幸運了！ -是啊
He has your eyes.
他眼睛和你的一樣
I mean, I know that's not possible, but he does.
雖然不可能, 不過真的是
We'll just get him cleaned up a bit.
把他擦乾淨些
Oh, my God, he's beautiful.
真是太美了
-Thank you so much. -I'm really happy for you guys.
-多謝你啊 -太為你們倆高興了
-How do you feel? -I'm tired.
-現在感覺如何？ -累啊
You don't have that much time to relax. The other one will be along in a minute.
沒多少時間可歇了, 下一個馬上就出來
I'm sorry, who should be along in a what, now?
抱歉……誰要出來？剛才你說啥？！
The next baby should be along in a minute.
下一個孩子馬上就出來
We only ordered one.
我們只訂了一個！
-You know it's twins, right? -Oh, yeah.
-你們知道是雙胞胎吧？ -才怪
These are the faces of two people in the know.
知道我們倆還能這副表情！
I can't believe you didn't know it's twins. This has never happened before.
怎麼可能不知道是雙胞胎？ 以前從來沒有過的
Well, gosh. That makes me feel so special and good.
啊！我現在感覺還真特別真爽啊
Did you know it was twins?
等等, 你知道是雙胞胎？
It's here in the paperwork we got from the clinic.
是啊, 俄亥俄送過來的文件裡面寫著呢
-Did anybody tell you? -I don't think so.
-有人告訴過你嗎？ -沒有啊
They did mention two heartbeats, but I thought it was just mine and the baby's.
不過確實提到了兩種心跳 我當時覺得應該就是我和孩子的吧
They said, "Both heartbeats are strong."
他們就一直說兩個心跳都很強
And I thought, "Well, that's good, because I'm having a baby."
我就覺得不錯啊, 因為我正懷著孩子哪
-This is unbelievable. -Twins actually run in my family.
-太難以置信了 -我家有雙胞胎的傳統的
Interesting.
真有意思哈
Can I see you for a second?
跟你談點事
-What do we do? -What do you mean, "What do we do?"
-現在咋辦？ -什麼咋辦？
Twins!
雙胞胎！
-Chandler, you're panicking. -Join me, won't you?
-錢德！你在發抖 -沒錯！和我一起抖吧！
What do you say we keep one and then just have an option on the other one?
我們留一個, 另一個給別人如何?
-We can't split them up. -Why not?
-怎麼可以分開啊！ -怎麼不行啊！
We could give each of them half a medallion.
給他倆一人半塊信物
And then years later, they'll find each other..
數年之後他們憑著信物重逢
and be reunited. I mean, that's a great day for everybody.
大團圓！ 到那時候大家該多開心啊
What if the person who adopts the other one is horrible?
如果領養另一個人的是壞蛋呢？
What if they're not? What if it's adopted by a king?
要不是呢？要是被某國王領養了呢？
Yeah. Because I hear the king is looking to adopt.
是哈, 聽說國王要領養個孩子！
Monica, we are not ready to have two babies.
莫妮卡, 咱倆沒想好要兩個孩子的
That doesn't matter. We have waited so long for this.
又有什麼關係！ 咱們等了這麼久
I don't care if it's two babies. I don't care if it's three babies.
我才不管是一個孩子還是兩個孩子！ 仨孩子都沒關係！
I don't care if the entire cast of Eight Is Enough comes out of there.
生出《八寶喜事》全劇組來都沒關係！
We are taking them home because they are our children.
一定要把他們帶回家 因為他們是咱們的孩子啊
Okay.
好吧
-Okay. -Okay!
-好 -好
Okay.
好了
It looks like we're about ready over here. Come on, Erica.
看來我們這裡準備好了! 來吧, 艾瑞卡.
Start pushing again now.
現在, 再推一次吧
-Here she comes. -She? It's a girl?
-女嬰也出來了！ -女嬰？！是個女孩？！
Yeah.
對
Well, now we have one of each.
現在一男一女了！
And that's enough.
然後就別再生了！
And then she said it was the perfect way to say goodbye.
後來她說那個是最好的告別方式
Oh, my God. What did you say?
天哪, 你說什麼了？
-Nothing. What do you say to that? -You've got to tell her how you feel.
-什麼都沒說 能說什麼啊？ -羅斯！一定要告訴她你的感受啊！
-No way. -Well, you can't just give up.
-不行！ -不能就這麼放棄她啊！
Is that what a dinosaur would do?
恐龍會這麼做嗎？
-What? -I'm just trying to speak your language.
-啥？ -我就是想用你們的語言和你說來著
Ross, Rachel doesn't know that you even wanna get back together.
瑞秋不知道你想復合
If she did, she might feel differently. She might not even go.
如果她知道 想法可能就會變啊, 也許就不會走了
-You really think so? -I'm telling you!
-真的？ -沒錯的
Oh, this is the part of the musical where there'd be a good, convincing song.
啊！如果是音樂劇的話, 現在就應該是高潮了
-Hi. -Can't a girl finish a song around here?
-嗨！ -死活就不讓我唱完了是吧
-Hey. -Hi. I dropped Emma off at my mom's.
-嘿 -剛把艾瑪交給我媽了
-Okay. -You're not taking her tonight?
-哦 -你今晚不帶艾瑪走？
We decided I'd set up, then my mom would bring Emma to Paris on Sunday.
不帶了, 我先去整理好 我媽星期天把艾瑪帶去
Eight-hour flight with a baby. Good luck, Mom.
哇！陪一歲小孩飛八個小時？祝你媽媽好運
You kidding? Eight hours with my mom talking about Atkins. Good luck, Emma.
開什麼玩笑, 陪我媽飛八個小時聽她嘮叨減肥食譜？ 還是祝艾瑪好運吧
All right. You know what? You're right. I should at least tell her how I feel.
你說得對, 至少要告訴她我的感受
-Ross. Wait, wait. -What? What?
-羅斯等一下！ -嗯？
Could you get me a muffin?
給我帶個鬆餅吧
-Rachel? -Yeah?
-瑞秋？ -嗯？
I know you're leaving tonight, but I just have to tell you.
我知道你今晚就走了 我就是想告訴你……
I love you.
我愛你
Now, I don't know if that changes your plans at all.
不知道你的計劃會不會因此改變……
But I thought you should know.
不過我覺得還是應該告訴你
Gunther.
甘瑟！
I love you too. Probably not in the same way.
我也愛你 不過和你愛我含義應該不一樣
But I do. And when I'm in a cafe having coffee..
但我真的愛你 每次我在咖啡屋喝咖啡
or I see a man with hair brighter than the sun..
或者看見誰的頭髮比太陽還亮
I'll think of you.
我都會想起你
-Bye, you guys. -Bye.
-回頭見 -拜~
Oh, my God!
天哪！
Unbelievable.
難以置信啊
-Hey, you know what might help? -I'm not getting you a muffin!
-我有個好主意…… -我不會給你拿鬆餅的！
Do you think they recognize each other from in there?
你覺得他倆從肚子裡出來, 認得出對方嗎？
Maybe. Unless they're like people who've lived in apartments..
也許, 不過也可能像倆多年的鄰居
next to each other for years, then one day they're pushed through a vagina..
突然有一天被擠出產道
and they meet.
終於見面了
We're going to take Erica to Recovery now.
我們現在帶艾瑞卡去休息了
There's something that we wanted to tell you.
有點事情我們要和你說
We decided to name the girl baby Erica.
我們決定給女孩起名為艾瑞卡
Oh, my God, that's just like my name!
天哪！這不和我名字一樣嗎？！
Son of a gun, it is.
TMD絕對是啊
Anyway, I'm gonna go get some rest.
總之我要先去休息了
I'm really glad I picked you guys. You're gonna make great parents.
能選中你們倆人我太高興了 你們倆一定會成為好父母的
Even Chandler.
甚至連錢德也是
-Okay, well, bye. -Bye.
-拜 -拜
-We'll call you. -Okay.
-給你打電話 -好
Have fun at church camp.
教會野營愉快啊！
-Look at these little bunnies. -I know.
-看看這些小傢伙 -是啊
You ready to trade?
想換了嗎？
-Okay. -Okay.
-好 -好
Okay. Let's see.
好, 這樣
-We could trade later. -Yeah, I'm good.
-一會兒再換吧 -沒問題
-Hey, what are you working on? -A "welcome home" sign for the baby.
-嗨, 幹嘛呢？ -寫歡迎標語呢
How sweet! Oh, is that the baby?
真不錯啊, 那畫的是嬰兒嗎？
No, I sat in the paint.
不是……我坐到顏料上了……
-Hey. -So did you talk to Rachel?
-嘿 -和瑞秋說了嗎？
-No. And I'm not going to. -What?
-沒說, 也不打算說了 -什麼？
-Why not? -She's just gonna shoot me down.
-為什麼啊 -因為她會拒絕我的
You saw what happened with Gunther. That did not look like fun.
你倆也看見甘瑟了 最後成那樣有意思嗎？
How can you compare yourself to Gunther?
你怎麼能把自己同甘瑟比？
I mean, sure, he's sexy in a more obvious way.
的確他從表面上來說比你更性感……
You have a relationship with her. You slept together last night.
你和瑞秋真正做過戀人啊 你們倆昨晚還一起過夜了
Yeah, and she still wants to go. It's pretty clear where she is.
沒錯！可是她還是要走！ 很清楚她現在是怎麼想的了
I know what you mean. I mean, sometimes..
我能理解, 有時候……
-Joe. -Damn it!
-啊, 喬…… -娘的！
If I were gonna tell her, I don't have to do it now.
即使我要和她說, 也不用現在吧
Okay? I'll be seeing her again. We've got time.
以後還能見, 有的是時間
No, you don't. She's going to Paris! She is going to meet somebody.
哪兒有？她是要去巴黎啊！ 她會遇見某個人！
Do you know how many hot guys there are in Paris? It's a city of Gunthers.
知不知道巴黎有多少帥哥？！ 全城滿大街都是甘瑟！
-Hey. -Hey.
-嘿 -嘿
-What do you have there? -Oh, I made a little something.
-手裡拿什麼呢？ -做了點東西
If I had more time to work on it, it'd be better, but..
時間充裕本來可以更好的
-Oh, my God, you did that yourself? -Honey, that's gorgeous.
-哇！你自己一個人弄的？ -這也太漂亮了吧 老公！
You know, the baby can't read, Mike.
嬰兒又不識字, 麥克！
Hi. The car service just got here. I can't believe they're not home yet!
去機場的車都來了, 他們怎麼還沒回來！
I have to catch my stupid plane. I want to see the baby.
我要趕飛機啊！我要看看孩子！
Monica just called from the cab. She said they should be here any minute.
莫妮卡剛才在車上打電話說馬上就到
-Apparently, there's some big surprise. -Yeah, did she sound happy about it?
-而且好像還要有個驚喜？ -她聽起來口氣高不高興？
Because my friend Ethel's baby was born with a teeny-tiny beard.
我有個朋友的孩子剛出生就有點鬍子
-Welcome home. -Oh, my God.
-歡迎回家！ -天哪！
-Oh, my gosh. -Hey.
-天哪！ -嘿
Hey.
嘿
Hey, so, what is the big surprise?
你說的驚喜是什麼啊？
-Oh, my God! -How did this..?
-天哪！ -這個問題
Okay, awkward question. The hospital knows you took two, right?
有點尷尬 不過醫院知道你們拿了兩個回來是吧？
-Yes. It's twins. -Oh, my.. They are so cute.
-知道, 是龍鳳胎！ -太可愛了啊
-Now, what kinds are they? -This is a boy. And that's a girl.
-誰是男誰是女？ -這是男孩, 那是女孩
Her name is Erica.
女孩名叫艾瑞卡
Hey, that pregnant girl's name was Erica.
那個懷孕的女孩不也叫艾瑞卡嗎？
Yeah. It's a shame you two didn't get to spend more time together.
沒錯……你們倆沒多相處相處太可惜了
Yeah, and we named the boy Jack, after Dad.
我們給男孩起名叫傑克, 隨老爸的
-He's gonna be so happy. -Jack Bing. I love that.
-他一定會高興極了的  -傑克.賓……這名字我喜歡！
It sounds like a '40s newspaper guy. You know, "Jack Bing, Morning Gazette.
聽起來像是四十年代寫新聞的啊  「傑克.賓, xxx
I'm gonna blow this story wide open."
看我怎麼渲染這條故事的！」
Oh, my gosh.
哦, 我的天
-So beautiful. -I want one.
-太美了！ -我也想要一個
Oh, yeah? Well, tell me which one. I'll try to slip it in my coat.
哦？告訴我哪個, 一會兒夾在大衣裡順走
Seriously. I mean, you want to make one of those?
說真的, 不想生一個？
-One? How about a whole bunch? -Really?
-一個？一堆怎麼樣？ -真的？
Yeah. We can teach them to sing, and we could be like the von Trapp family.
是啊 啊！可以教他們唱歌！ 就像《音樂之聲》那一家子一樣！
Only without the Nazis. Although that sounds kind of dull.
不過要把納粹部分刪去…… 但是這樣就沒意思了……
I can't believe this. If I don't leave now, I'm gonna miss my plane.
真是讓人不爽, 不過我要是 再不走就趕不上飛機了
-I'm so glad you got to see the babies. -Me too.
-你能見孩子們一面我真是太高興了 -我也是
I'm just sorry I'm not gonna be around to watch you two attempt to handle this.
真遺憾不能留下來看你照顧孩子手忙腳亂了
All right. Oh, I can't say goodbye to you guys again.
真的說不出告別的話
-I love you all so much. -Love you.
-我太愛你們了 -我也愛你
-We love you. -Call us when you get there.
-愛你 -到了打電話啊
I will. Ross, come here.
一定, 羅斯, 過來
I just want you to know..
我想告訴你...
last night..
昨晚……
I'll never forget it.
我永遠都不會忘記的
Neither will I.
我也不會
All right. Now I really have to go.
現在真的要走了
Okay, au revoir.
Au revoir！（法語「再見」）
They're gonna really hate me over there.
啊……等在巴黎我一定恨死自己了
So you just let her go?
你就這麼讓她走了？
Yeah.
嗯
-Hey, maybe that's for the best. -Yeah?
-這樣也許是最好的了 -真的？
Yeah. You know, you just.. Look, you gotta..
真的, 關於昨晚...
You gotta think about last night the way she does.
她怎麼想你也應該怎麼想
Okay? You know, maybe..
也許……
Maybe sleeping together was the perfect way to say goodbye.
也許在一起過夜 就是最好的告別了
They slept together?
他們一起睡覺了？
I was with you.
我和你一起的
-Now she'll never know how he feels. -Maybe that's okay, you know?
-可是這樣一來她就不知道他的感受了啊 -也許沒關係的
Maybe it is better this way.
也許這樣更好
I mean, now.. Now you can move on.
現在……現在你可以向前繼續生活了
I mean, you've been trying to for so long.
你已經努力適應這麼久了
Maybe now that you're on different continents..
現在你們倆身在不同的大陸……
-Right? -Yeah.
-是吧？ -是啊
Maybe now you can actually do it, you know.
也許你現在終於可以解脫了
You can finally get over her.
終於可以不再想她了
Yeah, that's true.
的確是這樣沒錯
Except..
可是……
-I don't want to get over her. -What?
-我不願意就這樣解脫 -什麼？
-I don't. I want to be with her. -Really?
-我不想……我想和她在一起 -真的？
-Yeah. I'm going to go after her. -Yeah, you are!
-嗯, 我去追她 -去吧！
Wait! Wait! Get your coat! Get your coat!
穿上外衣！穿上外衣！
-My coat. -This is so cool!
-外衣…… -太酷了！
I have no idea what's going on, but I am excited!
雖然一點都不明白咋回事  不過我現在太興奮了！
-What do you think she's gonna say? -I don't know.
-羅斯！你覺得她會怎麼說？ -不知道！
Even if she shoots me down, at least I won't spend my life wondering..
不過即便她拒絕我 我也不會餘生都活在猜測之中
what would have happened. Where is my coat?
我外衣哪兒去了！
You didn't bring one! My cab's downstairs. I'll drive you to the airport.
你根本就沒穿來！ 我車就在下面, 開車送你去機場！
-Wish me luck. -Hurry!
-大伙祝我好運！ -快！！！！！
Good luck!
祝你好運
Oh, my God.
天
Ross is going after Rachel. And you guys have babies.
羅斯去追瑞秋, 你們有了孩子
This is, like, the best day ever!
這就像是最棒的一天！
Why is there an ass-shaped paint stain on my couch?
我沙發上怎麼有屁股形狀的東西？
She asked you a question, Mike.
是你的問題, 麥克！
You really think we'll make it in time?
你真覺得我們能及時趕到?
Hey, I didn't have my license taken away because I drive carefully.
嘿, 我的駕照還沒被吊銷, 因為我開車很小心
-There's no seat belts! -That's okay. If we hit anything..
-沒安全帶？ -沒關係 一旦車撞到什麼東西...
the engine will explode, so it's better if you're thrown from the car.
引擎就會爆炸  相比之下還是被甩出去比較好
-All right, all right. Let's do this. -Okay!
-好！我們上！ -好!
-Hey! -80th and East End.
-嘿 -東區80號
-No. I don't take passengers. -The law makes you accept any fare.
-我不載客 -法律規定逢客必載的！
You don't understand. This cab isn't real.
你不明白, 這車本來就不是計程車！
What's your medallion number?
等我去投訴你, 你牌照號多少
My medallion number is, get out of the cab!
號碼是：滾出車去！
-What? -Get out of the cab!
-什麼？ -滾出車去！滾出車去！
Hey, you guys. Check this out.
嘿！大家看
-No! -Okay.
-不! -好
Oh, hey, can I give you guys my housewarming gift now?
哦！現在給你們喬遷禮怎麼樣？
-Now, that you can do. -All right.
-可以呀 -好
I have a question.
問個問題
Without looking under their diapers, can you tell them apart?
如果不看下面你能分清他們嗎？
Of course I can, I'm their mother.
當然可以, 我是媽媽啊
Oh, yeah? Okay. Which one is that one?
好, 那個是誰？
That's Jack.
是傑克
Jack's gonna have a tough time in high school with that vagina.
哇！傑克要去詹妮的學校了
Chick Jr.? Duck Jr.?
小小雞？小小鴨？
Don't hide from Mama!
別和媽媽捉迷藏！！
You can open your eyes now.
現在可以睜開眼睛了
-Are we off the bridge? -Yes!
-下橋了嗎？ -下了！
-Is the woman on the bicycle still alive? -Yeah, she jumped right back up.
-自行車上的老太太還活著嗎？ -活著！她及時跳開了！
-Oh, my God. Phoebe, slow down! -Do you want to get to Rachel in time?
-天哪！菲比！開慢點！ -你到底想不想及時追上瑞秋！
Yes, but I don't want to die in your cab.
想！不過我不想死在你車裡！
You should have thought of that before you got in!
上車之前你怎麼不想清楚！！！
-Tollbooth. -What?
-收費站 -什麼？
Tollbooth!
收費站!
Four bucks. There are quarters in the glove compartment.
四塊錢, 雜物箱裡有零錢
Hurry!
快點！！！！！！
Okay.
哦
Damn, that window's clean.
媽的, 窗戶怎麼這麼乾淨！
We were wondering what was taking so long..
我們還說你拿禮物這麼半天還不回來
but now we understand. You were doing this.
現在才知道你在幹這個……
Okay. I wanted to surprise you, but..
我本想給你們個驚喜的……
For your housewarming gift, I got you a baby chick and a baby duck.
作為喬遷禮, 送給你們一隻小雞一隻小鴨！
Really? You got us a chick and a duck?
真的？給我們小雞小鴨？
Oh, great. Just what you want for a new house with infants. Bird feces!
太好了, 家裡有嬰兒, 鳥糞正合適啊！
But they must've jumped off the table. Now they're gone!
一定是從桌子上跳下去了, 現在都不見了啊！
Don't worry, we'll find them.
別著急, 慢慢找
Actually, I'm gonna go check on the twins.
我去看孩子去了
Oh, God! What did I just step on?
啊!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 我剛才踩著什麼了！
It's okay. It's just an egg roll.
沒事了, 就是個蛋卷
You stepped on my egg roll?!
你竟敢踩著我的蛋卷！
I'm sorry. I didn't know to look for Chinese food on the floor.
抱歉, 誰會想到地上會有中國菜！
Just put it on a plate and leave.
放到盤子裡, 然後快走
-Okay. Let's find these birds. -All right.
-好了. 開始找吧 -好
Wait, wait. You hear that?
等等！聽到了沒？
-They're in the table! -Well, that can't be good.
-啊！在桌子裡！ -這可不妙了！
-We gotta get them out of there! -How?
-必須要取出來！ -怎麼取？！
Maybe we can lure them out. You know any birdcalls?
也許能引誘他們出來, 你知道鳥怎麼叫嗎？
Oh, tons. I'm quite the woodsman.
當然了, 我就是干伐木工的
Well, maybe we can just tip the table a little.
把桌子一頭抬起來點也許管用
Joey, wait! The ball!
喬伊等一下！球還沒...
So, what do we do?
現在怎麼辦！！
Maybe we can open this up somehow.
不清楚……也許邊上什麼地方能打開吧
Okay.
好
No. It's all glued together.
不行啊, 都粘上了
Does that mean we have to bust it open?
也就是說要……硬撬開？
-I don't know. Maybe. -Oh, my God.
-不知道……也許吧 -天哪！
I know. It's.. It's the foosball table.
我明白……這可是足球桌啊
All right, you know what? We don't have a choice.
沒有辦法了
It's like I would have said in that sci-fi movie if I'd have gotten the part.
就像我在一部科幻電影裡面的台詞一樣, 如果我當初贏到角色的話……
Those are our men in there, and we have to get them out..
「裡面有人！必須要救出來！」
even if I have to sacrifice the most important thing in my life..
「即使要犧牲我生命中最重要的東西--
my time machine.
我的時間機器……」
-Did that movie ever get made? -It did not.
-這電影拍出來了沒？ -根本沒拍……
Jack Weinberg, white courtesy phone. Jack Weinberg.
-Ross, where are you going? -To talk to Rachel.
-羅斯！你去哪裡？ -去找瑞秋啊
Isn't that why we took a ride in the death cab?
所以我才坐死亡計程車來的
You're walking up to her at the gate?
你就直接去登機口？
Have you never chased anyone through the airport before?
以前在沒在機場追過人？！
Not since my cop show got canceled.
我的警察戲鏡頭被取消之後就沒有過了……
You have to get a ticket to get past security.
必須先買票才能通過安檢
-What? We're never gonna make it. -Not with that attitude. Now, haul ass!
-那就趕不及了啊！ -保持這種氣勢！快滾過來！
Okay, if you could all walk slower, that'd be great.
大家再走慢點就好了
-Madame, your passport, please. -Oh, my God.
-（法式英語）小姐, 看一下您的護照？ -天哪！
I was afraid I wouldn't remember my high school French.
我還害怕高中學的法語都忘乾淨了呢！
But I understood every word you just said.
你剛才說的每個字我都聽明白了！
-Your boarding pass, please. -Oh, sure.
-您的登機牌？ -哦, 當然
Shoot, I had it. Oh, I can't believe this.
好的……找不到…… 本來在啊……真叫人……
-Madame, if you don't have your.. -I have it, I have it!
-小姐, 如果您沒有…… -我有我有我有我有！！！
Okay, I can't find it, but I remember that I was in seat 32C..
哎呀, 找不到, 不過我清楚記得 我的座位號是32 C
because that's my bra size.
因為我罩杯號就是這個
You must have your boarding pass..
-小姐, 您必須要有登機牌, 否則……
You know what? If I was in 36D, we would not be having this problem.
告訴你, 我要是36 D, 就沒這麼多麻煩了！
-Hi. I need a ticket. -Just one?
-您好, 我要買一張票 -就買一張？
I drive you here, and I don't get to see how it works out?
我開車這麼大老遠送你過來 不能看看結局啥樣？
-Fine. Two tickets. I need two tickets. -We're on our honeymoon.
-好吧, 兩張, 我買兩張票！ -我們在度蜜月呢
-And the destination? -I don't care. Whatever's the cheapest.
-目的地是？ -隨便, 最便宜的吧
I'm so lucky I married you.
我嫁給你真是太走運了哈
Oh, shoot. Damn it. Where is it?
啊！靠！媽的！哪裡去了！
I found it. I found it. I told you I would find it.
啊！找到了找到了！哈！ 找到了！早和你說了我有！
In your face. You're a different person.
你是另外一個人了..
Sorry.
抱歉
Okay. Flight 421, Paris.
4-21航班, 巴黎
-I don't see it. Do you see it? -No. Did we miss it?
-找不到, 你呢？ -我也找不著 錯過了？
No, no, it's impossible. It doesn't leave for another 20 minutes.
不可能,20分鐘後才起飛的
Maybe we have the flight number wrong.
航班號錯了吧
God.
天
-Hello. -Hey, it's me. Here's Ross.
-嗨 -嗨, 是我, 給你羅斯
What?
什麼？
Hey. Hey, listen..
嗨！聽著……
You wouldn't believe the cute noises the twins are making. Wait, listen.
天啊, 倆孩子的聲音太可愛了！羅斯你聽！
But Monica..
但是莫妮卡
Monica. Monica. Monica.
莫妮卡？……莫妮卡！莫妮卡！莫妮卡！莫妮卡!
I'm sorry. They were doing it before.
抱歉, 他倆剛才還出聲來著啊
-That's all right. Listen, listen. -Oh, wait, wait. Here they go again.
-莫妮卡！聽著…… -等等！又來了！！
Monica. Monica. Monica.
莫妮卡！莫妮卡！莫妮卡！莫妮卡！莫妮卡！
-Monica? -Isn't that cute?
-莫妮卡？ -可愛吧！
That is precious! Listen..
可愛死了！！！聽著
-I need Rachel's flight information. -Oh, okay.
-我要瑞秋的航班信息 -哦, 好
-All right, it's flight 421. Leaves at 8:40. -I have that. It's not on the board.
-4-21航班,8點40起飛  -是啊, 就是這個, 看板上找不到
That's what it says here. Flight 421. Leaves at 8:40. Newark Airport.
這裡就是這樣寫的啊,4-21航班  8點40起飛, 紐瓦克機場
-What? -Newark Airport.
-什麼？ -紐瓦克機場
-Why? Where are you? -JFK.
-怎麼了？你們在哪裡？ -肯尼迪機場……
Don't worry, you guys! We're gonna get you out of there!
別著急！會把你們救出來的！
And we're also gonna buy you tiny bird hearing aids.
然後再給你們買小鳥用助聽器……
Okay. Here goes.
好, 來了……
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
I need to say goodbye to the table first.
我要先跟桌子告別
I understand.
我理解
Okay.
好
Table..
桌子！
you have given us so many great times.
你曾經給予我們太多的歡樂時光
And you guys, Jordan, Victor, Joel..
你們大伙……喬丹、維克多, 還有喬
All of you guys. What can I say?
你們所有人, 我得說
You guys make us look good.
是你們讓我倆更有形象
-You want to say anything? -I don't know.
-你想說什麼？ -不清楚……
Except that, for one last time..
不過, 最後一次……
Good game. Good game. Good game.
幹得好……幹得好……幹得好……幹得好……
Good game.
幹得好
Okay. Here we go.
好吧, 來, 動手
I can't do it.
我下不了手
Well, I can't do it either.
我也下不了手啊！
-Hey. Did you find them? -Yeah. They're stuck inside the table.
-找到沒？ -在桌子裡面哪！
And we have to bust it open, but neither of us can do it.
必須要撬開, 不過我們倆都下不去手！
Oh, well, sure. It's got to be so hard.
是啊……太難了……
I'll do it. Give me.
我來吧, 給我！
Phoebe!
菲比！！！
No, no, no!
不要啊！！！！！！！
Wow, I've never gone this fast before.
以前從沒開這麼快過！！
Phoebe, forget it, okay? Newark is, like, an hour away.
菲比！！算了吧！紐瓦克 一個小時才能到
There's no way we'll make it in time.
根本趕不上
-She's got her cell. You could call her. -I am not doing this over the phone.
-她拿著手機呢！打電話！ -我不要在電話上談
You don't have any other choice.
你沒其他辦法了啊
-Hello? -Rachel. Oh, good.
-喂? -瑞秋？太好了！
By the way, did you just get on the plane?
對了你是不是剛上飛機？
-Yeah. -We would have caught her..
-是啊 -不管怎樣提一句..
if we were at the right airport.
如果機場沒去錯
-Rachel, hang on. -No. No. No.
-瑞秋, 等著 -不不不
Phoebe, is everything okay?
菲比？你那邊不要緊吧？
Actually, no. No. You have to get off the plane.
啊, 事實上, 有點事情 你必須下飛機
-What? Why? -I have this feeling that..
-啊？為什麼？ -我有種感覺
something's wrong with it. Something is wrong with the left phalange.
飛機有問題, 左「弗蘭基」有毛病
Oh, honey, I'm sure there's nothing wrong with the plane.
親愛的, 飛機肯定沒問題的
Look, I have to go. I love you, and l will call you the minute I get to Paris.
馬上要起飛了, 我愛你 一到巴黎就打電話
-What was that? -Oh, that was just my crazy friend.
-你剛才說什麼？ -哦, 我的瘋朋友
She told me to get off the plane because she had a "feeling" that there..
讓我下飛機 因為她就是感覺到
was something wrong with the left phalange.
飛機左「弗蘭基」有毛病
-Okay. That doesn't sound good. -Oh, I wouldn't worry about it.
-聽起來可不妙吧 -不用擔心
She comes up with this stuff, and she's almost never right.
她老是這樣, 而且幾乎從沒對過
-But she is sometimes. -Well..
-也就是說她也有對的時候？ -啊...
-What are you doing? -I can't take this plane now.
-你要幹嗎？ -這飛機我不能坐
-Excuse me, sir. Where are you going? -I have to get off this plane.
-對不起, 先生, 您去哪裡？ -我要下飛機
Her friend has a feeling something's wrong with the left phalange.
她朋友感覺到 飛機左「弗蘭基」有毛病
Could I get some peanuts?
請給我拿點花生好嗎？
-What's wrong with the plane? -There's nothing wrong.
-飛機怎麼了？ -飛機一點異常都沒有
-The left phalange. -There's no "phalange."
-左「弗蘭基」有毛病了 -根本就沒有什麼「弗蘭基」！
Oh, my God. This plane doesn't even have a phalange.
天哪！這破飛機連「弗蘭基」都沒有！
-I'm not flying on it. -Please sit down.
-我不飛了 -女士, 請您坐好
-What's going on? -We're getting off. There is no phalange!
-出什麼事情了？ -我們都下去！飛機上根本就沒有「弗蘭基」！
This is ridiculous. I..
太荒謬了吧, 我
Yeah, okay.
啊, 隨便吧
All right. My job here is done.
好了, 工作完成
That was impressive.
你太……強了
Yeah. You didn't even use the tools for most of it.
大部分連工具都沒用就弄下來了
Yeah, they were just slowing me down.
啊, 工具太礙事了
All right. I gotta get back to the babies. See you girls later.
好啦, 我回去看孩子了 你們倆個丫頭一會兒見
-Sorry about the table, man. -Yeah.
-真抱歉阿, 桌子這樣了  -嗯
You gonna buy a new one?
要買新的嗎？
Probably not. No.
也許不了……不會了
I don't know how much I'm gonna want to play after you go.
你走後我估計也不怎麼會去玩了
-At least we got these little guys out. -Yeah.
-至少這兩個小傢伙救出來了 -是啊
We were worried about you.
我們還擔心你們哪
I guess I better get used to things crapping in my hand, huh?
以後就多習慣有東西在我手裡拉屎吧
I'm gonna miss these little guys.
我會想你們的, 小傢伙
It was nice having birds around again.
再養養鳥還真挺不錯的
Hey, you know what? Maybe we should keep them here with you.
這樣吧, 它們就交給你了
-What? -Yeah. We got a lot going on right now.
-什麼？ -嗯, 我們現在也忙得要死
And plus, here, they'd have their own room.
而且這裡也有它們的房間啊
I could get a goose!
還可以再養只鵝！
You know, I think you're set with the poultry.
我覺得家禽類這兩隻就夠了
Thanks, man. You hear that, you guys?
多謝了  聽到沒有？
You're gonna get to stay here. And it's good..
你們要留在這裡啦！ 而且這樣也挺好的
you know, because..
因為
Because now you have a reason to come visit.
你就有理由多回來看看了
I think there may be another reason.
其實還有一個理由
So..
那個……
Awkward hug or lame cool-guy handshake?
尷尬的擁抱呢…… 還是假酷男握手呢
Yeah, well, you know, lame cool-guy handshake.
啊, 還是假酷男握手吧
-Ma'am, I assure you, the plane is fine. -And you fixed the phalange?
-女士, 我想您保證, 飛機沒有問題  -「弗蘭基」也裝好啦？
Yes. The phalange's fixed.
沒錯, 裝好了
In fact, we've put a whole lot of extra phalanges onboard, just in case.
而且 還又帶了一個備用的以防萬一
Paging Mr. Anderson. Mr. Josh Anderson.
-Where is she? -I don't see her.
-她在哪兒？ -看不到
-Rachel! Rachel Green! -There she is!
-瑞秋！！瑞秋.格林！！！ -她在那裡！！
Rachel! Rachel!
瑞秋！！！！！！
-Whoa, do you have a boarding pass? -No. I just have to talk to someone.
-先生, 您有登機牌嗎？ -沒有, 我就是要找裡面的一個人說句話……
I'm sorry. You need a boarding pass.
對不起, 沒有登機牌不能再往前走了
-No, no. But you don't.. -Rachel!
-不 不 不…… -瑞秋！！！
What? Oh, my God. What are you guys doing here?
嗯？啊？你們在這裡幹嘛呢？
Okay. You're on.
輪到你了
What? What, Ross? Okay, you're scaring me. What's going on?
怎麼了？怎麼了羅斯？ 你嚇到我了, 出什麼事了？
-Okay. Thing is.. -Yeah.
-嗯  我想說的是... -什麼
-Don't go. -What?
-不要走 -什麼？
Please, please stay with me. I am so in love with you. Please don't go.
留下來和我在一起, 我太愛你了  求求你不要走
-Oh, my God. -I know. I know.
-天哪 -我知道, 我知道
I shouldn't have waited till now to say it, but.. That was stupid, okay? I'm sorry.
不應該拖到現在才說的 我太笨了, 對不起
But I'm telling you now. I love you.
不過我現在和你說：我愛你
-Do not get on this plane. -Miss, are you boarding the plane?
-不要上飛機 -小姐？您是否要上飛機？
Hey, hey.
嘿
I know you love me. I know you do.
我知道你愛我, 我都知道
-Miss. -I..
-小姐？ -我……
I.. I have to get on the plane.
我要上飛機
-No, you don't. -Yes, I do.
-不要, 別上飛機 -我要上
-No, you don't. -I do. They're waiting for me, Ross.
-不要, 別上飛機 -都等著我呢, 羅斯
I can't do this right now, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我現在真的不能這麼做, 對不起 對不起
Rachel.
瑞秋
I'm so sorry.
真的對不起
I really thought she'd stay.
我本來以為她會留下的……
I know.
我知道
I'm sorry.
我很遺憾
Well, that's it.
那麼, 就這樣了
Everything's packed.
好了, 收拾完畢
-This is weird. -I know.
-啊, 感覺有點怪啊 -我明白
Yeah.
嗯
Does this mean there's nothing to eat?
啊……也就是說沒吃的了？
I put three lasagnas in your freezer.
我在你冰箱裡面放了三盤意大利寬麵條
I love you.
我愛你
-Hey. -Hey. Did you guys make it in time?
-嘿 -怎樣？趕上了嗎？
Yeah, yeah. He talked to her, but she got on the plane anyway.
趕上了, 他跟她說了 不過她最後還是上了飛機
Where's Ross?
羅斯呢？
He went home. He didn't want to see anybody.
回家了, 他誰也不想見
Ross. Hi, it's me.
「羅斯, 嗨 是我」
I just got back on the plane, and I just feel awful.
「我剛回到飛機上」 「我現在感覺太難受了」
That is so not how I wanted things to end with us.
「我絕不希望我們之間這麼就完了」
It's just that I wasn't expecting to see you.
「只是……只是我根本沒料到你會出現」
And all of a sudden you're there and saying these things.
「猛一下子你就來了, 還說那些話……」
Now I'm just sitting here and thinking..
「我現在坐在這裡, 靜靜地想……」
of all the stuff I should have said and I didn't.
「想我應該說卻沒有說出口的話」
I mean, I didn't even get to tell you that I love you too.
「我甚至都沒跟你說我也愛你」
Because of course I do. I love you.
「因為, 我真的愛你」
I love you.
「我愛你」
What am I doing? I love you.
「我到底在幹什麼？我愛你！」
I've got to see you. I've got to get off this plane.
「我要見你, 我要下飛機！」
Oh, my God.
天哪
-Okay, excuse me. -Miss, please sit down.
-「打擾一下！」 -「小姐, 請坐下」
No, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry, but I need to get off the plane.
「真對不起, 我要立刻下飛機！
-I need to tell someone that I love them. -I can't let you off.
-去告訴他我愛他！」 -「小姐, 現在不能下飛機」
Let her off the plane!
讓她下飛機！！！！！
You have to take your seat.
「請您務必坐好」
Oh, please, miss. You don't understand.
「求求你了, 你不明白！」
Try to understand!
你不明白！！！！！！
Come on, miss, isn't there any way that you can just let me off the..?
「小姐, 有沒有辦法讓我能下……」
No! No!
不要！！！！！！！！！
Oh, my God. Did she get off the plane? Did she get off the plane?
上帝啊, 到底下沒下飛機？到底下沒下飛機？！
I got off the plane.
我下飛機了……
You got off the plane.
你下飛機了……
I do love you.
我愛你, 真的
I love you too, and I am never letting you go again.
我也愛你, 再也不會讓你走了
Okay. Because this is where I want to be. No more messing around.
我也希望留在這裡, 再也不要有遺憾
-I don't want to mess this up again. -Me neither. We're done being stupid.
-我不想再搞砸了 -我也不想, 我們已經蠢過一次了
Okay. It's you and me, all right? This is it.
只有你和我, 好不好,  只有你和我
This is it. Unless we're on a break.
只有你和我 除非我們是在分手中……
Don't make jokes now.
現在可不是開玩笑的時候
Okay, please be careful with that. It was my grandmother's. Be careful.
請小心點, 這是我祖母的,  請務必小心
Thank you.
多謝
If that falls off the truck, it wouldn't be the worst thing.
如果這玩意兒掉下去了, 也沒什麼大不了的
I know.
是啊
Seems smaller somehow.
看起來好像小了一圈
Has it always been purple?
一直都是紫色的？！
Look around, you guys. This was your first home.
小傢伙們, 看看四周吧 這裡是你們第一個家
And it was a happy place, filled with love and laughter.
一個幸福的家 充滿了愛心與歡笑
But more important, because of rent control, it was a frigging steal.
更重要的是 租金管制簡直就是明搶啊
Hey, do you realize that, at one time or another, we all lived in this apartment?
嗨, 你們有沒有意識到, 我們每個人都在這裡住過
Oh, yeah. That's true.
還真是
I haven't.
我沒有
What about that summer during college that you lived with Grandma..
你大學有一年暑假過來和祖母住
and you tried to make it as a dancer?
然後你想靠跳舞來掙錢……
Do you realize we almost made it 10 years without that coming up?
你有沒有意識到, 這都是十年前的骨灰了你還往外挖？
Oh, honey, I forgot. I promised Treeger that we'd leave our keys.
啊, 親愛的, 我差點忘了  我答應崔格把鑰匙留下
Oh, okay.
好
-So I guess this is it. -Yeah.
-都結束了？ -是啊
I guess so.
應該是吧
This is harder than I thought it would be.
比想像中的還要難啊！
Oh, it's gonna be okay.
會好的
Come on.
好了
Do you guys have to go to the new house now, or do you have some time?
你們倆是馬上去新房子還是能擠出點時間來嗎？
We got some time.
還有點時間
-Okay. Should we get some coffee? -Sure.
-去喝杯咖啡怎麼樣？ -好啊
Where?
去哪兒喝？